JESSICA ELLIS

123 Main Street, Orlando, FL 12345 j.ellis@youremail.com (012) 345-6789 Dedicated and professional child care provider with over 12 years of experience caring for toddlers, infants, and preschoolers. Proven track record in creating fun educational and recreational activities for children. Maintained a 5-star rating on Google and Yelp for the past seven years. Trusted by parents to take care of their children in a safe and nurturing environment.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

CHILD CARE PROVIDER

ABC Fun Day Care Center, Orlando, FL | September 2015 - Present

- Supervise and care for up to 17 children aged 6 weeks to 4 years
- Create fun indoor and outdoor activities to facilitate learning and recreational play
- Ensure a high standard of care for all children in the facility
- Establishing a training program to upgrade staff skills and ensure professionalism

FREELANCE CHILD CARE PROVIDER

Orlando, FL | June 2008 - August 2015

- Babysat infants and small children for families in the Orlando area in the evening and during weekends
- Picked up young children from school and assisted with their homework while their parents were at work
- Fed, bathed, and got children ready for bed when their parents had to work late

EDUCATION

ASSOCIATES OF ARTS DEGREE IN EARLY CHILDHOOD EDUCATION

The University Of Orlando Orlando, Fl | September 2006 - June 2008

KEY SKILLS

- Activity planning and supervision
- Organized
- Good with small children
- Excellent communication
- Friendly

CERTIFICATIONS

- CPR
- AED
- First Aid